{
	"questions": [
		{
			"id": 1,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy single question 1",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 4"
		},
		{
			"id": 11,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy single question 2",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 4"
		},
		{
			"id": 12,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy single question 3",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 2"
		},
		{
			"id": 13,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium single question 1",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 1"
		},
		{
			"id": 14,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium single question 2",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 3"
		},
		{
			"id": 15,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium single question 3",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 1"
		},
		{
			"id": 20,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard single question 1",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 1"
		},
		{
			"id": 21,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard single question 2",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 3"
		},
		{
			"id": 22,
			"type": "single",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard single question 3",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": "option 1"
		},
		{
			"id": 2,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy multiple question 1",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [2, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 9,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy multiple question 2",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [1, 2]
		},
		{
			"id": 10,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy multiple question 3",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [2, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 23,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium multiple question 1",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [2, 0]
		},
		{
			"id": 24,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium multiple question 2",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [1, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 25,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium multiple question 3",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [0, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 26,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard multiple question 1",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [2, 0]
		},
		{
			"id": 27,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard multiple question 2",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [1, 3]
		},
		{
			"id": 28,
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard multiple question 3",
			"options": ["option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
			"correct_answer": [1, 2]
		},
		{
			"id": 3,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy boolean question 1",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": true
		},
		{
			"id": 29,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy boolean question 2",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": false
		},
		{
			"id": 30,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "easy boolean question 3",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": true
		},
		{
			"id": 4,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "boolean question medium 1",
			"options": ["true", "false"],
			"correct_answer": false
		},
		{
			"id": 31,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium boolean question 2",
			"options": ["true", "false"],
			"correct_answer": true
		},
		{
			"id": 32,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "medium boolean question 3",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": false
		},
		{
			"id": 5,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "boolean question hard 1",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": true
		},
		{
			"id": 8,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard easy boolean question 2",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": false
		},
		{
			"id": 16,
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "hard single question 3",
			"options": [true, false],
			"correct_answer": false
		}
	]
}
